{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "respuesta": "lunatico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "respuesta": "estomago",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "respuesta": "ingenio",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "respuesta": "pinocho",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "respuesta": "quincena",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "respuesta": "pantalon",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "respuesta": "enfadado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "respuesta": "bizcochuelo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "respuesta": "entretenido",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "respuesta": "pantano",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "respuesta": "sombrilla",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "respuesta": "sorpresa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "respuesta": "pepino",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "respuesta": "el gordo|y el flaco",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "respuesta": "conocimiento",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "respuesta": "revelar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "respuesta": "me chupa|un huevo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "respuesta": "termometro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "respuesta": "leer entre|lineas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "respuesta": "escama",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "respuesta": "entrenadora",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "respuesta": "llave|francesa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "respuesta": "fe de|erratas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "respuesta": "encubierto",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "respuesta": "colaboracion",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "respuesta": "confirma",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "respuesta": "pancarta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "respuesta": "el canal de|la mancha",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "respuesta": "maniatico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "respuesta": "circulo|vicioso",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "respuesta": "agua|oxigenada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "respuesta": "la torre|de pisa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "respuesta": "leche|cortada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "respuesta": "emparedado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "respuesta": "triangulo de|las bermudas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "respuesta": "circulo|polar artico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "respuesta": "guardar|bajo llave",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "respuesta": "todo sobre|ruedas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "respuesta": "escalpelo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "respuesta": "limonada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "respuesta": "florencia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "respuesta": "aire|comprimido",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "respuesta": "ascensor",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "respuesta": "cantero",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "respuesta": "soldado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "respuesta": "berenjena",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "respuesta": "vino|blanco",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "respuesta": "estetoscopio",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "respuesta": "palometa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "respuesta": "cucharita",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "respuesta": "mas vale tarde|que nunca",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "respuesta": "analfabeta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "respuesta": "alfa romeo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "respuesta": "climatizado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "respuesta": "comida|rapida",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "respuesta": "camaleon",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "respuesta": "fuego|cruzado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "respuesta": "votar en|blanco",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "respuesta": "caleidoscopio",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "respuesta": "polenta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "respuesta": "empanada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "respuesta": "resfrio",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "respuesta": "picara",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "respuesta": "emperador",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "respuesta": "apila",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "respuesta": "edad media",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "respuesta": "canoso",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "respuesta": "lenteja",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "respuesta": "bolchevique",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "respuesta": "paraguas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "respuesta": "carajo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "respuesta": "cantantes",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "respuesta": "impresa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "respuesta": "paciente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "respuesta": "negrita",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "respuesta": "caracol",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "respuesta": "coliflor",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "respuesta": "mejor reir|que llorar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "respuesta": "dependencia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "respuesta": "porcelana",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "respuesta": "sobrevolar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "respuesta": "verde",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "respuesta": "viento en|popa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "respuesta": "sobrevivir",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "respuesta": "microscopico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "respuesta": "corazonada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "respuesta": "epico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "respuesta": "tesoro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "respuesta": "sintaxis",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "respuesta": "sin ton|ni son",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "respuesta": "empezar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "respuesta": "rueda de|prensa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "respuesta": "jueves|santo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "respuesta": "plano|inclinado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "respuesta": "desencuentro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "respuesta": "mal educado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "respuesta": "pariente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "respuesta": "pentagrama",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "respuesta": "ni fu ni fa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "respuesta": "pilates",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "101",
      "respuesta": "polinesia|francesa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "102",
      "respuesta": "armonicamente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "103",
      "respuesta": "picante",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "104",
      "respuesta": "dios|mediante",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "105",
      "respuesta": "sincope",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "106",
      "respuesta": "singapur",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "107",
      "respuesta": "docena",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "108",
      "respuesta": "mate|cocido",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "109",
      "respuesta": "endosa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "110",
      "respuesta": "postres|helados",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "111",
      "respuesta": "puente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "112",
      "respuesta": "aruba",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "113",
      "respuesta": "casino",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "114",
      "respuesta": "todo bajo|control",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "115",
      "respuesta": "novela",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "116",
      "respuesta": "venado",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "117",
      "respuesta": "barcelona",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "118",
      "respuesta": "rio de|janeiro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "119",
      "respuesta": "los angeles",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "120",
      "respuesta": "sevilla",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "121",
      "respuesta": "estados|unidos",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "122",
      "respuesta": "montevideo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "123",
      "respuesta": "calculo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "124",
      "respuesta": "paris",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "125",
      "respuesta": "malaga",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "126",
      "respuesta": "durazno",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "127",
      "respuesta": "venezuela",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "128",
      "respuesta": "pino",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "129",
      "respuesta": "mykonos",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "130",
      "respuesta": "monterrey",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "131",
      "respuesta": "cartagena",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "132",
      "respuesta": "asuncion",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "133",
      "respuesta": "falacia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "134",
      "respuesta": "colombia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "135",
      "respuesta": "noruega",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "136",
      "respuesta": "caracas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "137",
      "respuesta": "san diego",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "138",
      "respuesta": "palma de|mallorca",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "139",
      "respuesta": "sahara",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "140",
      "respuesta": "receta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "141",
      "respuesta": "isla|margarita",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "142",
      "respuesta": "bolivia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "143",
      "respuesta": "arabia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },

    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "144",
      "respuesta": "damasco",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "145",
      "respuesta": "tierra del|fuego",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "146",
      "respuesta": "mar del|plata",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "147",
      "respuesta": "salubre",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "148",
      "respuesta": "cataratas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "149",
      "respuesta": "rebota",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "150",
      "respuesta": "lisboa",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "151",
      "respuesta": "barbados",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "152",
      "respuesta": "canada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "153",
      "respuesta": "calamar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "154",
      "respuesta": "pandemonio",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "155",
      "respuesta": "papagayo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "156",
      "respuesta": "mayordomo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "157",
      "respuesta": "calvario",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "158",
      "respuesta": "merienda",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "159",
      "respuesta": "monarca",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "160",
      "respuesta": "nomina",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "161",
      "respuesta": "mariguana",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "162",
      "respuesta": "pajaro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "163",
      "respuesta": "repollo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "164",
      "respuesta": "remora",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "165",
      "respuesta": "recien|casados",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "166",
      "respuesta": "reglamenta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "167",
      "respuesta": "testosterona",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "168",
      "respuesta": "pirata",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "169",
      "respuesta": "remar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "170",
      "respuesta": "portero",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "171",
      "respuesta": "sanamente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "172",
      "respuesta": "remodela",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "173",
      "respuesta": "resaltar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "174",
      "respuesta": "arcabuz",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "175",
      "respuesta": "petalo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "176",
      "respuesta": "postiza",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "177",
      "respuesta": "piston",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "178",
      "respuesta": "premeditar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "179",
      "respuesta": "monoculo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "180",
      "respuesta": "resorte",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "181",
      "respuesta": "platano",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "182",
      "respuesta": "sotana",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "183",
      "respuesta": "superfluo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "184",
      "respuesta": "tartamudo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "185",
      "respuesta": "silaba",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "186",
      "respuesta": "recorre",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "187",
      "respuesta": "tramposo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "188",
      "respuesta": "terremoto",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "189",
      "respuesta": "torpedo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "190",
      "respuesta": "taladra",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "191",
      "respuesta": "salpicadura",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "192",
      "respuesta": "aguacate",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "193",
      "respuesta": "alarma",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "194",
      "respuesta": "arroba",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "195",
      "respuesta": "velada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "196",
      "respuesta": "solista",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "197",
      "respuesta": "viatico",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "198",
      "respuesta": "marron",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "199",
      "respuesta": "velocimetro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "200",
      "respuesta": "tributo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "201",
      "respuesta": "barranco",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "202",
      "respuesta": "boliviano",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "203",
      "respuesta": "batidora",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "204",
      "respuesta": "reciente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "205",
      "respuesta": "boa vista",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "206",
      "respuesta": "cachorro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "207",
      "respuesta": "cuba",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "208",
      "respuesta": "recinto",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "209",
      "respuesta": "ampliamente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "210",
      "respuesta": "margarita",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "211",
      "respuesta": "bastonazo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "212",
      "respuesta": "borracha",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "213",
      "respuesta": "barbuda",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "214",
      "respuesta": "boludo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "215",
      "respuesta": "camarada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "216",
      "respuesta": "artesanalmente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "217",
      "respuesta": "barbara",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "218",
      "respuesta": "alaska",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "219",
      "respuesta": "marsella",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "220",
      "respuesta": "osaka",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "221",
      "respuesta": "diametro",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "222",
      "respuesta": "acalorada",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "223",
      "respuesta": "sotano",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "224",
      "respuesta": "batahola",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "225",
      "respuesta": "malasia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "226",
      "respuesta": "socorre",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "227",
      "respuesta": "anatomicamente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "228",
      "respuesta": "colmar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "229",
      "respuesta": "la paz",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "230",
      "respuesta": "ciudad del|cabo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "231",
      "respuesta": "cucuta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "232",
      "respuesta": "panama",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "233",
      "respuesta": "potente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "234",
      "respuesta": "margen",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "235",
      "respuesta": "pantalla",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "236",
      "respuesta": "diacono",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "237",
      "respuesta": "calibre",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "238",
      "respuesta": "bombacha",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "239",
      "respuesta": "tormenta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "240",
      "respuesta": "soltero",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "241",
      "respuesta": "pupilas",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "242",
      "respuesta": "helsinki",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "243",
      "respuesta": "marchita",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "244",
      "respuesta": "milagroso",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "245",
      "respuesta": "varsovia",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "246",
      "respuesta": "parlamento",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "247",
      "respuesta": "calcuta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "248",
      "respuesta": "camaron",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "249",
      "respuesta": "asfalto",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "250",
      "respuesta": "cantina",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "251",
      "respuesta": "cancun",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "252",
      "respuesta": "sierra leona",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "253",
      "respuesta": "osamenta",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "254",
      "respuesta": "resguardar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "255",
      "respuesta": "piojo",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "256",
      "respuesta": "relata",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "257",
      "respuesta": "campera",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "258",
      "respuesta": "soledad",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "259",
      "respuesta": "vibracion",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "260",
      "respuesta": "amorosamente",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "261",
      "respuesta": "camara",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "262",
      "respuesta": "barril",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "263",
      "respuesta": "desconcierto",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Acertijos",
      "pregunta": "264",
      "respuesta": "diezmar",
      "categoria": "Acertijos"
    }
  ]
}
